Let's see how to use Views Remarketing in your Sponsored display campaigns to engage
audiences who have viewed specific product detail pages, which can help you drive awareness
and consideration, even convert missed sales.
In your Sponsored display campaign, choose Audiences as your targeting strategy.
Then, pick Views Remarketing.
Include audiences who have viewed your advertised product's detail pages or the detail pages
of similar products.
You'll see these already added by default, and you can keep or remove any of them.
Plus, you can reach shoppers who view detail pages in various categories, use our suggestions
or search for ones yourself, set the look back window to specify the window of time
for Views.
You can refine any of them by features like price or star rating.